

#### **ABOUT MYSELF**

I am 33 years old. I am active and creative man. I'm ready to learn something new. I am not afraid of heavy tasks and responsibilities. I am finishing the career in Internal troops of interior ministry. Looking for the new challenges.

#### **CONTACTS**

Phone (Viber, Telegram):

+375-25-778-91-66

E-mail:

BayarevichAleh@yandex.ru

Skype:

Boyarevich

Linkeln:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/aleh-bayarevich-1415091b0/

\/K·

https://vk.com/boyarevich

GitHub:

https://github.com/BayarevichAleh

#### **HOBBIES**

Robotics Guitar Building my own house

# **BAYAREVICH ALEH**

# Python-developer (Back-end)

#### **SKILLS**

- Python (Django, Django REST, NumPy, JSON, CSV)
- C (development of programs from microcontrollers: AVR, PIC, STM32; GUIinterface for devices; data exchange between devices: UART, I2C, RS485, SPI; development of systems on more than 50 client devices, EEPROM, Flash-memory)

Example C-code for MCU: https://github.com/BayarevichAleh/MCU.git

- GIT
- Docker
- CSS, HTML, Bootstrap
- Linux (terminal, bash, GCP)
- English (A2)

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Internal troops of interior ministry (2006 - 2020)

2018 - 2020 (Head developer devices of security)

Main responsibilities:

- Development of technical task
- Development of device of security
- Development of architecture of systems
- Development of program for microcontroller in C-language
- Testing of device
- Preparing documentation for release device

2013 - 2018 (Head of service devices of security)

Main responsibilities:

- Planning work
- Putting tasks
- Work with documentation

2010 - 2013 (Technician of development devices of security)

Main responsibilities:

- Making prototype of devices
- Testing prototype of devices

2008 - 2010 (Technician of devices of security)

Main responsibilities:

- Installation and maintenance systems of security and videoview

2005 - 2006 (Soldier)

Effective soft (2005 - 2006)

Flash-animator

Main responsibilities:

- Creation flash-movies

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Coding school "TeachMeSkills"

05.2020 - 09.2020

Course: Python developer

Description: Python, Git, SQLite, PostgresSQL, Django, HTML, CSS, JSON

My diploma project (In developing):

https://github.com/BayarevichAleh/BayarevichAleh.git

### **Belarus State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics**

2014 - 2016

Specialty: Computer technology design of electronic systems Specialization: Magister of technique and technology

#### **Belarus State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics**

2008 - 2014

Specialty: Technical security

Specialization: Engeneer-electromechanic

#### Minsk State High Radioengineering College

2008 - 2014

Specialty: Technical exploitation of radio electronics devices

Specialization: radiotechnician

# **COURSES, CERTIFICATES AND OTHERS**

#### **TeachMeSkills**

What learned:

- Python
- OOP
- PIP
- Git / Github
- Decorators
- JSON, CSV
- PostgreSQL / MySQL / SQLAlchemy
- Numpy / scipy / pandas
- Django / Flask /
- Django REST
- HTML / CSS / JS
- Docker



# 

## Stepik.org

What learned:

- Linux
- Terminal
- Tmux
- Filesystem
- Nano, Vim
- Bash
- Virtual server
- Curl







## **GeekBrains**

#### Tests:

- Python. Beginning level
- Python. Level 1
- Regular expressions and OOP in Python

# My diploma project from "TeachMeSkills"

GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/BayarevichAleh/BayarevichAleh.git">https://github.com/BayarevichAleh/BayarevichAleh.git</a>

#### What used:

- Django
- PostgreSQL
- Mixins
- CKeditor
- HTML / CSS / Bootstrap
- Send\_mail
- Django ORM
- Customisation of admin
- Extending the user model
- Forms
- Validation